我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
不是想讓你傷心
Not trying to make you feel bad
我從這裡飄到那
I'm floating from here to there
我不依戀過往事
I'm not attached to what I had
從我記憶以來，我就在旅行了
I've been on the road since I could remember
穿越 Equestria
Traveling Equestria
我會給你表演
I'll give you a show
我會給你我心
I'll give you my heart
但我從一開始就在痛
But I've been aching since the start
一直把自己賣給惡魔
Been selling myself to the devil
只為了讓你驕傲
Just to see you proud of me
我自己一人好久了
It's been so long since I've been alone
但還是需要你盯著
Still I need your eyes on me
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
不是想讓你傷心
Not trying to make you feel bad
我從這裡飄到那
I'm floating from here to there
我不依戀過往事
I'm not attached to what I had
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
我是個風中的蝴蝶
I'm a butterfly in the wind
不能待在同一處
Can't stay in one place
因為我不敢面對恐懼
'Cuz these fears I just can't face
在友誼的路上
On the road to friendship
你了解自己更多
You learn a lot about yourself
我足夠嗎？他還好嗎？
Am I enough? Will she be okay?
我是否值得呢，我會否進步，今天？
Am I really worth it, will I do better today?
噢，我一直跟自己起鬧
Ooh, I've been fucking with myself
直至今日，都偽裝別人
Forced to be somepony else until now
一直躲在黑暗中
All this time in the dark
還是繼續走吧
Just keep on moving on
我是個遊民...
I'm a nomad...
一直都只為了不要難過
All this time just to not feel sad
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
不是想讓你傷心
Not trying to make you feel bad
我從這裡飄到那
I'm floating from here to there
我不依戀過往事
I'm not attached to what I had
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
我是個風中的蝴蝶
I'm a butterfly in the wind
不能待在同一處
Can't stay in one place
因為我不敢面對恐懼
'Cuz these fears I just can't face
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
不是想讓你傷心
Not trying to make you feel bad
我從這裡飄到那
I'm floating from here to there
我不依戀過往事
I'm not attached to what I had
我只是個遊民
I'm a nomad
我是個風中的蝴蝶
I'm a butterfly in the wind
不能待在同一處
Can't stay in one place
因為我不敢面對恐懼
'Cuz these fears I just can't face